You've already won once
I'm serious
I didn't believe in choices before
Many things weren't up to me
But now I want to choose for once
Choose what
Choose you
Not because you helped me
Not because you know my future
But because the current Fu Chenzhou wants to
choose the current Su Mengyao
Will Mrs. Fu accept
I accept
Chairman, the verification process is complete
Hospital records, orphanage files
Origin of old items, old left wrist injury
And the final identity matching results
They are all here
Does Fu Chenzhou know the results
Not yet, Mr. Fu said once the results are out
he wants to see them with Mrs. Fu
Ask them to come up